Hello guys, I am Rajesh Mishra, I
heartily welcome you to your own channel.
As you must have understood from the thumbnail,
in today's video we are going to know
about ICC Labad's Elevate plan. Do
you know what is inside the Elevate plan,
which no one in the industry has yet,
which only Elevate plan is going to give
us. What could be such a
feature which no other company has yet in health insurance
and which
only IIC Labad is launching first in the
industry.
Any idea, any guesses, please comment while
we proceed further. Elevate
with Inflate Sum Insured
Option. Yes, you are hearing it right.
Option to choose unlimited sum insured
cover. 5 lakh, 20 lakh, 25 lakh, 50 lakh, one crore,
three crore, five crore, 10 crore.
You can take insurance for sum issues up to unlimited. The
name of that plan is Elevate and
it has many unique features. Stay tuned
till the end of the video. A very interesting plan has
come.
Welcome to Health Insurance Tso.
Personalize and Infit It feels like magic, that is,
everything is unlimited, there is
no gapping here, there is no limit, everything is
unlimited,
Infa reset means your
plan will keep getting reset for unlimited time, Infa
claim amount may be Rs.
100 crores, and
if you have taken a policy of Rs. 10 lakhs, then also that
claim will be given, that too with cashless Infit
[ __ ]
Bonus, that is, Power Booster add-on,
your sum in share will keep increasing every year,
we have already told you about the same Infit sum in share, that is,
you
can take sum in it for unlimited time, no matter how many
claims come, there is no tension,
so the most unique features of this plan are
Infit Care, one
Infit claim amount for your selected
claim, if you have taken a policy of Rs. 10 lakhs and
your claim is of Rs. 50 crores,
you can take this once in the entire policy tenure, yes,
you are hearing it absolutely right,
unlimited times  No gapping, no limit,
power booster gets a collect bonus of 100%
every year relative to the claim for the infinite
period, that is, if you take the feature of power booster, then
whatever sum you purchase for the policy, it will
increase by 100% in the next year and that too for unlimited time.
Let's take an example, if you
take a policy of Rs 10 lakh and take power booster next year,
that policy will be of Rs 20 lakh, then next year 30 lakh 40 lakh 70 lakh 80 one crore
one crore 10 lakh one crore
20 lakh, like this for unlimited time, the policy sum every year will be
infinite sum with
unlimited,
optional of limited coverage, that is,
we used to get limited coverage earlier, now we will get
unlimited, if we buy infinite
sum or unlimited sum, then jump start is the
best feature, get waiting period due to
jump start, that is, the waiting period for pre-assisting diseases is 1
year  It will be reduced to
30 days with this plan.
Now which S&PD is Pre-Assisting
Disease, we will know about it in detail later. So, the
amazing feature till now is Elevate
with Infit Sum Is option, that is, you
can select the sum assured for unlimited time, there is
no capping, there is no limit,
you can do whatever you want,
Elevate with Infit Sum Is Boost, Industry
First, whatever it may be, every
year if you
take the Infit Care feature, Power Booster, what happens with it,
policy of Rs 10 lakh in five years, Rs 50 lakh
in two years, Rs 1 crore in 20 years, Rs 2 crore and it will keep
multiplying and every
year Infit
Claim, that is, if you purchase the Infit Claim feature, it is being
given like an add-on with this plan. If you
leave a sum of Rs 10 lakh, your first claim is of Rs 5
lakh, second is of Rs 2 lakh and
after that if your claim is Rs 50 lakh or Rs 1
crore or two  No matter how much the claim is, the
company will pay you the claim once in a lifetime, that too
cashless whole
amount. What a unique feature this is. Do you understand that
you have taken a policy of Rs. 10 lakhs, taken Innate Care
Addition along with it
and your claim is of Rs. 20 crores, then the company will pay that
claim for you.
Jump start means the
waiting period for pre-assisting diseases will be reduced from one year to
30 days. Now the diseases covered in this are diabetes, asthma,
hyperlipidemia, obesity,
hypertension, these are the five diseases. If there is
anything regarding this, then your PD will be reduced
from one year to 30 days.
Sir, we have discussed everything, now tell me how much discount you will get. You will get a
discount in this if you
take a long term policy, up to 15%
if your civil score is good. Again you can get a
discount of up to 15%. If
you get the renal done 30 days before the
due date, then you will
get a discount of up to 2.5% on that as well and 10%
in the network proof partner network.  If you get
treatment done and you take D on then
you will get a discount of 10% in this also.
Wellness discount up to 30% means
you will get wellness discount in all the activities that you do for your health
but the maximum capping of discount is
30%, you will not get more than that
and for wellness discount you have to
download Il Tech Care.
Now let's know about this plan.
What is in-built in it, if we do
not take any D on anything then what is covered in it
or what are the in-built features. Inpatient up
to 50% single AC private room pre and
post cover. This is a very good feature, that is, you will
get complete coverage in it 90 days before and 180 days after the illness. There
is reset benefit unlimited times. Any person any where i.e. same
person sameness is also covered.
Guaranteed collect bonus or 20% bonus every year. You will get
up to
100% donor expenses in this. The
waiting period for up to 50% abdominal surgery is
two years and  That too is completely covered. All
re-hospitalization expenses up to the hospital
are completely covered. The
entire plan you take is covered for pain
treatment, that too is covered for the entire time. There is no capping. You
can also get cover up to Rs. 10 lakh for domestic road ambulance. There is
no capping for day surgery up to Rs. 10 lakh for AYUSH
patient treatment. There is no capping in AYUSH as well, there is no
limit.
Surrogacy and TO
site is the maximum cover that the company has provided in this.
If the mother faces some complications,
then we will cover up to Rs. 5 lakh.
How can you avail ambulance service?
You can also avail the benefit of ambulance service through Il Tech Care P
and
for discounts also, you will have to download Il Tech Care P
and in it you are
offered very good deals and discounts.
For renewal also, you will get the
reward points of wellness only through Il Tech Care
P. If there is a health
assistant, then you can also avail that through Il Tech
Care P. E-consultancy is also available.  You can avail
tele-consultancy. Now let us know
about the waiting period in this. The initial
waiting period is 30 days. The
waiting period for pre-assisting diseases is
normally 8 months. The
waiting period for specific diseases is 24 months. The
waiting period for critical illness is 90 days. The
waiting period for maternity is usually 24 months. The
waiting period for basic surgery is 24 months. The waiting period for
diabetes, hypertension, cardiac condition, etc.
If he/she is not in PD, there is a
waiting period of 90 days.
Now
about who can avail this plan,
if the age of the entry age person is between 18 years to 125
years, then it means yes, you are hearing it absolutely right, that is,
every age person
can avail this plan. The sums being offered in this are
75, 50, 3 CR and then
unlimited sum.  These are the insured options
given. The policies that you can take are for one
year, two years, three years. The
limit of family floater is for two
adults and three kids.
Child is considered as dependent till 30
years if policy is taken with parents, that is,
now children will be considered up to 30 years old
because nowadays it has been seen that marriages happen
at the age of 30 plus, so till the time your
children will be covered in your policy,
after that they will have to be separated.
These were the unique features of this plan. If you have
any doubt, any query or
want to purchase a plan, then you can contact us.
Thank you.